Paul Baran Papers M1817
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- AssortedClippings Date:080801 (Container 210, Folder 29)
  Denial of Service Attacks: An Emerging Vulnerability for the 'Connected' Network (White Paper prepared by Sonic Systems) 281 0 xxxx Nancy's Office Empty, formerly Nancy's office misc. (refilled) and hanging file folders 209 1 980710 Computer Manuals Network Drawings 209 2 981211 Computer Manuals Unresolved Problems 209 3 023102 Computer Manuals Epson Stylus Photo R800 Printer 209 4 030101 Computer Manuals Microsoft Office 2003 - Student and Teacher 209 5 030101 Computer Manuals Names and Emails (to be entered) 209 6 030101 Computer Manuals Different Email Addresses 209 7 030410 Computer Manuals Black binder of email addresses 209 8 030603 Computer Manuals Network Solutions 209 9 030608 Computer Manuals Aladdin Stuffit Deluxe 8.0 209 10 040128 Computer Manuals FinePixViewer 209 11 040720 Computer Manuals Sony Remote Control 209 12 040721 Computer Manuals Fugi Film Finepix S7000 209 13 041124 Computer Manuals Computer Passwords 209 14 050112 Computer Manuals Patent Pro 209 15 050124 Computer Manuals On Line Accounts 209 16 050520 Computer Manuals HP Printer CLJ 3700n 209 17 050806 Computer Manuals PDF Converter 3 209 18 060630 Computer Manuals Sony Vaio SX230 209 19 060706 Computer Manuals Buffalo Link Station 209 20 070104 Computer Manuals Logitec Wireless Keyboard & Mouse 209 21 080831 Computer Manuals Microsoft Office 2007 - Small Business (Nancy's Office) 209 22 080831 Computer Manuals Microsoft Office 2007 - Small Business (Paul's Office) 209 23 080831 Computer Manuals XP Computer Invoice 209 24 080831 Computer Manuals Samsung Sync Master Disk 209 25 080831 Computer Manuals Pioneer DVR-216 Digital Video Recorder 209 26 080831 Computer Manuals Microsoft XP Disk 209 27 080831 Computer Manuals ASUS P5K Motherboard (Paul's Office) 209 28 080831 Computer Manuals ASUS P5K Motherboard (Nancy's Office) 209 29 080831 Computer Manuals Haupage Win-TV-HVR 150 Model 1196 209 30 080831 Computer Manuals Microsoft XP Disk 254 1 760109 Aud/Video Tapes NSA/NBS/Hellman/Diffie/Baran (audio) 254 2 760109 Aud/Video Tapes NSA/NBS/Hellman/Diffie/Baran (audio) 254 3 760109 Aud/Video Tapes NSA/NBS/Hellman/Diffie/Baran (audio) 254 4 760109 Aud/Video Tapes NSA/NBS/Hellman/Diffie/Baran (audio) 254 5 760109 Aud/Video Tapes NSA/NBS/Hellman/Diffie/Baran (audio) 254 6 931101 Aud/Video Tapes The Internet: Logging into the Future Today 254 7 990429 Aud/Video Tapes Franklin Institute: Awards Ceremony & Gala 254 8 010101 Aud/Video Tapes Franklin Institute Awards 254 9 010101 Aud/Video Tapes Franklin Institute Awards & Animation Elements 254 10 010101 Aud/Video Tapes Understanding the Internet (Andrew Cochran Asso, Canada) 254 11 010101 Aud/Video Tapes Internet - Canadian Discovery Channel 254 12 010101 Aud/Video Tapes BBC Eyewitness to History 254 13 000131 Aud/Video Tapes The Internet Behind the Web 254 14 000131 Aud/Video Tapes The Internet Behind the Web 254 15 000131 Aud/Video Tapes The Internet Behind the Web 254 16 000131 Aud/Video Tapes The Internet Behind the Web 265 1 910514 Misc. Telebit: Telebit Corp. Introduces Dedicated Communications Server"
- Historic Data Date:801020 (Container 211, Folder 1)
  3Com Corp. ,Ethernet Product Plans and Preliminary Prospectus
- Historic Data Date:830328 (Container 211, Folder 2)
  Ridge Vineyards Capital Stock - 5,000,000 shares
- Historic Data Date:840331 (Container 211, Folder 3)
  Telebit Corp. Quarterly Report to Shareholders
- Historic Data Date:840406 (Container 211, Folder 4)
  Telebit Corp. Documents to Shareholders re: stock distributed by Cabledata
- Historic Data Date:840723 (Container 211, Folder 5)
  Telebit, Notice of Annual Meeting of Shareholders; Shareholders List
- Historic Data Date:840810 (Container 211, Folder 6)
  Equatorial Common Stock, 10,000 shares; Martin Marietta Acq, Annual report
- Historic Data Date:870213 (Container 211, Folder 7)
  Nat.Research Council, PB Appt. to Bd on Telecommunications & Computer Apps, Nat. Acad. of Sciences
- Historic Data Date:880001 (Container 211, Folder 8)
  Telebit Annual Report to Stockholders
- Historic Data Date:891128 (Container 211, Folder 9)
  IBM - Packet Technologies
- Historic Data Date:900001 (Container 211, Folder 10)
- Historic Data Date:901006 (Container 211, Folder 11)
  IEEE 1990 Medals Presentation, Toronto
- Historic Data Date:901001 (Container 211, Folder 12)
  Research Newsletter, Southern California Edison (Netcomm Matures)
- Historic Data Date:910208 (Container 211, Folder 13)
  Integrated Energy Group, Preliminary Report on Metricom
- Historic Data Date:920001 (Container 211, Folder 14)
  Amoco Corp. Annual Report to Stockholders
- Historic Data Date:951213 (Container 211, Folder 15)
  Southern California Edison, Review of NetComm Final Report
- Historic Data Date:980001 (Container 211, Folder 16)
  Metricom Report
- Historic Data Date:990322 (Container 211, Folder 17)
  Concepts into Reality: Ideas into Companies
- Packet Swit Date:640001 (Container 213, Folder 1)
  On Distributed Communications, Sponsored by the USAF under Project RAND
- Packet Swit Date:890817 (Container 213, Folder 2)
  UCLA - Act One, Symposium on Very High Speed Information Networks
- Packet Swit Date:990831 (Container 213, Folder 3)
  Sigcomm '99, Tutorial T1, Technical History of the Internet
- Packet Swit Date:020308 (Container 213, Folder 4)
  IEEE Com Mag Paper Inputs (Paul Baran)
- Packet Swit Date:620415 (Container 216, Folder 1)
  Leonard Kleinrock's Paper (1961)
- Packet Swit Date:620901 (Container 216, Folder 2)
  On Distributed Communications Networks
- Packet Swit Date:620925 (Container 216, Folder 3)
  Routing Procedures in Communications Networks. Part I: Random Procedures 216 4 640801 Packet Swit On Distributed Communications: V. History Alternative Approaches and Comparisons"
- Packet Swit Date:670910 (Container 216, Folder 5)
  Computer Network Meeting at Pentagon
- Packet Swit Date:740311 (Container 216, Folder 6)
  On the Development of a Packet Switching Industry in the US (Cerf)
- Packet Swit Date:890817 (Container 216, Folder 7)
  US Patent 5,115,433, Methods for Routing Packets in a Packet Communication Network
- Packet Swit Date:890817 (Container 216, Folder 8)
  1989 Act One Pioneer Award from UCLA's Computer Science Dept.
- Packet Swit Date:900505 (Container 216, Folder 9)
  An Interview with Paul Baran conducted by Judy O'Neill, Charles Babbage Institute
- Packet Swit Date:910726 (Container 216, Folder 10)
  Supporters of PB's nomination for the Marconi International Fellowship
- Packet Swit Date:941024 (Container 216, Folder 11)
  UCLA - Computer Science Dept. Act Two: A Silver Jubilee
- Packet Swit Date:941024 (Container 216, Folder 12)
  Email from Stephen White re: Cerf v. Cern
- Packet Swit Date:960901 (Container 216, Folder 13)
  Why It Wasn't Built (draft) - (URLs for old papers)
- Packet Swit Date:961018 (Container 216, Folder 14)
  Misc - Emails from Tony Hearn, Bruce Smith. "Examination of a Distributed Network"
- Packet Swit Date:961031 (Container 216, Folder 15)
  On the Origins of Packet Switching - original art by PB
- Packet Swit Date:961031 (Container 216, Folder 16)
  On the Origins of Packet Switching by PB (master)
- Packet Swit Date:970521 (Container 216, Folder 17)
  The Internet After Thirty Years By Peter Denning
- Packet Swit Date:990831 (Container 216, Folder 18)
  PB Bio (and picture) for Sigcomm '99
- Packet Swit Date:990831 (Container 216, Folder 19)
  Notes, maps, schedules, messages from the conference
- Packet Swit Date:990831 (Container 216, Folder 20)
  New Research: A Supplement to the Proceedings (published by Harvard)
- Packet Swit Date:990831 (Container 216, Folder 21)
  SIGCOMM Paper (SIGCOMM '99 Tutorial Session Notes, Boston)
- Packet Swit Date:990831 (Container 216, Folder 22)
  PB Talk at Sigcomm Packet Switching Mechanisms
- Packet Swit Date:990831 (Container 216, Folder 23)
  Computer Communication Review: Applications Technologies, Architectures and Protocols
- Packet Swit Date:990901 (Container 216, Folder 24)
  "A Brief History of the Future: The Origins of the Internet" by John Naughton
- Packet Swit Date:990923 (Container 216, Folder 25)
  SRI - Arpanet History. Email from Donald Nielson
- Packet Swit Date:990928 (Container 216, Folder 26)
  You, Too, Invented Net? Get in Line. Boston Globe (by Ross Kerber)
- Packet Swit Date:991024 (Container 216, Folder 27)
  Interview with PB as conducted by David Hochfelder, IEEE History Center
- Packet Swit Date:000104 (Container 216, Folder 28)
  IEEE Internet Award (Completed form, bio and letters)
- Packet Swit Date:000124 (Container 216, Folder 29)
  Recipient of IEEE Third Millennium Medal (submitted by IEEE Communications Soc)
- Packet Swit Date:000111 (Container 216, Folder 30)
  Live Chat with "The Founding Fathers of the Internet," History Channel
- Packet Swit Date:000126 (Container 216, Folder 31)
  Report of the 1999 IEEE Internet Award Committee (from David Walden, Chair)
- Packet Swit Date:000131 (Container 216, Folder 32)
  Katie Hafner, regarding Leonard Kleinrock and his role in packet switching
- Packet Swit Date:010418 (Container 216, Folder 33)
  Intro to Davies' Paper; "An Historical Study of the Beg of Packet Switching; "Award acceptance
- Packet Swit Date:010901 (Container 216, Folder 34)
  Communications of the ACM (includes article by Leonard Kleinrock on "Breaking Loose")
- Packet Swit Date:011001 (Container 216, Folder 35)
  National Academy of Engineering Awards, 2001
- Packet Swit Date:011108 (Container 216, Folder 36)
  A Paternity Dispute Divides Net Pioneers (by Katie Hafner) plus misc, Kleinrock, etc.
- Packet Swit Date:020001 (Container 216, Folder 37)
  The Internet - Past, Present and Future: The Beginnings of Packet Switching by Yusung Kim
- Packet Swit Date:020117 (Container 216, Folder 38)
  Caspian Networks Losing Valuation but Hope Remains Larry Roberts (New York Times)
- Packet Swit Date:041006 (Container 216, Folder 39)
  Email from Thelma Estrin re: An Insightful look at the "facts" - start of the Arpanet
- Packet Swit Date:041016 (Container 216, Folder 40)
  PB letter to Les Earnest with attached paper PB wrote in 2002
- Packet Swit Date:041016 (Container 216, Folder 41)
  PB letter to Bob Metcalfe re: Donald Davies paper and a paper PB wrote in 2002
- Packet Swit Date:041201 (Container 216, Folder 42)
- Packet Swit Date:041201 (Container 216, Folder 43)
  UCLA "Building Global Connections" Article on "Cybervision"
- Packet Swit Date:041209 (Container 216, Folder 44)
  PB's paper "Does Leonard Kleinrock's Dec. 1962 Dissertation Anticipate Packet Switching?
- Packet Swit Date:050101 (Container 216, Folder 45)
  SIGCOMM Paper (Drawings)
- Packet Swit Date:050101 (Container 216, Folder 46)
  The Biggest Company on Earth: A Profile of AT&T by Sonny Kleinfield
- Packet Swit Date:050101 (Container 216, Folder 47)
  Why Packet Switching Works (Misc. drawings)
- Packet Swit Date:050101 (Container 216, Folder 48)
  Katie Hafner 's drafts (2)
- Metricom Date:880428 (Container 220, Folder 1)
  Information on Pump Control and Efficiency (various articles)
- Metricom Date:930719 (Container 220, Folder 2)
  Mobile Data Report - "Establishment of Campus Wide Networks Emph. Low Cost Airtime"
- Metricom Date:930802 (Container 220, Folder 3)
  Mobile Data Report - "Metricom's Success in Market Will Hinge on Business Case"
- Metricom Date:940628 (Container 220, Folder 4)
  Release: "Ricochet Wireless Data Network Reaches Cupertino - Full Service"
- Metricom Date:930520 (Container 220, Folder 5)
  Release: "Metricom Announces $4 Million UtiliNet Order"
- Metricom Date:890001 (Container 220, Folder 6)
  Metricom Communication Systems Communications for a New Era
- Metricom Date:920501 (Container 220, Folder 7)
  Prospectus - 1,500,000 Shares, Common Stock; Cowen & Co, Needham & Co.
- Metricom Date:921113 (Container 220, Folder 8)
  Landis & Gyr - Letter of Intent to Provide Utility Metering & Communications Products
- Metricom Date:920001 (Container 220, Folder 9)
  Annual Report - (Year of transition from private to public company)
- Metricom Date:930610 (Container 220, Folder 10)
  UtiliNet Customer Apps. (from BECO, ComEd, FPL, Georgia Power, MPS, PG&E, SCE, WPL)
- Metricom Date:870526 (Container 220, Folder 11)
  Outlet (publication of SCE): Edison Enters New Age of Customer Research
- Metricom Date:860710 (Container 220, Folder 12)
  Interesting Concepts - Best Relay Stations, etc.
- Metricom Date:860309 (Container 220, Folder 13)
  Overview: Company, Market, Products, Customer Competition, Mgmt, Fin. Analysis, etc.
- Metricom Date:850001 (Container 220, Folder 14)
  Clipping Book (from WSJ, Forbes, Electronics IEEE, GE Publications, etc.
- Metricom Date:860418 (Container 220, Folder 15)
  Ltr. To Caskey, PG&E (in response to the draft)
- Metricom Date:851205 (Container 220, Folder 16)
  Preliminary Business Plan (Loaned to Schroder Venture Managers)
- Metricom Date:880516 (Container 220, Folder 17)
  A Measure and Optimization Controller for Centrifugal Pumping Systems
- Metricom Date:940714 (Container 220, Folder 18)
  Board Meeting (Pres. Report, Corporate Matters Finances, Operations, UtiliNet, Rocochet)
- Metricom Date:940927 (Container 220, Folder 19)
  Board Meeting (Pres. Report, Corp. Matters, UtiliNet, Ricochet, FCC & Frequency Issues
- Metricom Date:930401 (Container 220, Folder 20)
  The Company & Its Technology (plus Marketing & Sales Review, Impressions of Metricom)
- Metricom Date:930101 (Container 220, Folder 21)
  Employee Handbook: Employee Guidelines - 4th Edition
- Metricom Date:930203 (Container 220, Folder 22)
  Wireless Data Networks for Portable Communications (the MG Development Prog.)
- Metricom Date:950125 (Container 220, Folder 23)
  Board Meeting, Palm Springs (R&D, Other Spectrum, Increase Network Speed, etc.
- Metricom Date:840301 (Container 220, Folder 24)
  Pump Efficiency (graphs, charts, and figures)
- Metricom Date:910001 (Container 220, Folder 25)
  Three Resumes (Michael Ballard, Robert Hillman, Donald Wood)
- Metricom Date:911216 (Container 220, Folder 26)
  Townsend and Townsend, Re: U. S. Patent #4,939726 (routing packets)
- Metricom Date:880401 (Container 220, Folder 27)
  Crop Notes (Monterey County) Re: Improving Pumping Plant Efficiency
- Metricom Date:941030 (Container 220, Folder 28)
  Leading the Way in Wireless Intelligence: A Leader in Digital Wireless Data Communi.
- Metricom Date:921105 (Container 220, Folder 29)
  Sterling Project Analysis: Balance Sheet, Income Statement, Cash Flow, Investments
- Metricom Date:840201 (Container 220, Folder 30)
  A Universal Controller for Parallel Pumps with Variable-Frequency Drives (by Hammond)
- Metricom Date:870001 (Container 220, Folder 31)
  Motorola Semiconductor: Power Effect Transistor Module - Energy Management Series
- Metricom Date:840301 (Container 220, Folder 32)
  Berkeley: Submersible Turbine Pumps Performance Curves; Measuring Depth
- Metricom Date:880428 (Container 220, Folder 34)
  Fax from Roger Hass - Study of pumps and the agricultural electric bill
- Metricom Date:840001 (Container 220, Folder 35)
  IA 20 (probably IEEE) Information on Industry Applications
- Metricom Date:720001 (Container 220, Folder 36)
  Rodger Walker, "Pump Selection: A Consulting Engineer's Manual" Ann Arbor Science
- Metricom Date:850001 (Container 220, Folder 37)
  Digital Control Patterns of the CSI and other info. Pp 619 - 624 (book unknown)
- Metricom Date:880401 (Container 220, Folder 38)
  Monterey County Crop Notes Benefits of improving pumping plant efficiency
- Telebit Date:920319 (Container 222, Folder 1)
  Annual Report, Proxy Statement and new brochure on Net Blazer product line
- Telebit Date:920225 (Container 222, Folder 2)
  Proxy Resumes (Baran, Ballard, Himsworth, Johnson, Kramlich, Burton)
- Telebit Date:920225 (Container 222, Folder 3)
  IMC Trip Report, Salt Lake; Dave de Heer and Denis Aull
- Telebit Date:920214 (Container 222, Folder 4)
  Financial Management Report Dec, 1991(Summary P & L, Balance Sheet, Cash Flow,etc)
- Telebit Date:920225 (Container 222, Folder 5)
  Octocom Meeting - discussion of joint marketing opportunities
- Telebit Date:920213 (Container 222, Folder 6)
  Board Meeting, Feb. 13, 1992 (Agenda, Q4 Proforma Results, Employee Stock Options)
- Telebit Date:920402 (Container 222, Folder 7)
  Press kit (Fact Sheet, Annual Report, Dial-up Connectivity, News releases, etc.)
- Telebit Date:920415 (Container 222, Folder 8)
  Annual Meeting April 15, 1992, Plus Engineering Update, & Revenue by Product
- Telebit Date:920424 (Container 222, Folder 9)
  Stock Price (Pacific Growth Equities) & Organizational Charts
- Telebit Date:920618 (Container 222, Folder 10)
  Board Meeting (composition, marketing re-org, inter. objectives, qtr forecast, Cisco, legal)
- Telebit Date:911029 (Container 222, Folder 11)
  Board Meeting (corp strategy, investor relations, M&A, Hayes, compensation, audi, etc)
- Telebit Date:920428 (Container 222, Folder 12)
  Financial Report for March, 1992; Jeffrey Hilber, Corporate Controller
- Telebit Date:920225 (Container 222, Folder 13)
  IMC Trip Report, Salt Lake: Dave de Heer and Denis Aull
- Telebit Date:920225 (Container 222, Folder 14)
- Telebit Date:840919 (Container 222, Folder 15)
  DCA/Telebit Data Systems Joint Venture Business Plan; Minutes & Oct. 1984 Financials
- Telebit Date:840601 (Container 222, Folder 16)
  Competitive Analysis (Objectives, Approach, Competitors, Results)
- Telebit Date:840718 (Container 222, Folder 17)
  Second Round Financing: Wilson Sonsini's Draft of Series B Preferred Stock
- Telebit Date:840716 (Container 222, Folder 18)
  Appraisal of DCA/Telebit Joint Venture; Plus Overview of Second Round Financing Status
- Telebit Date:840630 (Container 222, Folder 19)
  Second Quarterly Report (Engineering & Development, Marketing, Finance)
- Telebit Date:840723 (Container 222, Folder 20)
  Board Meeting (Minutes, Pres. Report, Business Plan, Finances, 2nd Round Financing, etc)
- Telebit Date:840529 (Container 222, Folder 21)
  Agenda, Bridge Financing, New Offices, Stock for Employees, Prof. Services Agreement
- Telebit Date:840206 (Container 222, Folder 22)
  New Enterprise Asso. Stock Purchase; Heller, Ehrman, White & McAuliffe
- Telebit Date:840301 (Container 222, Folder 23)
  Business Plan (Goals, Strategies & Obj; Products; Market Anal; Sales; Eng, Manuf; Adm. )
- Telebit Date:840112 (Container 222, Folder 24)
  Memos from Johnson, Newsfront Article, Miscellaneous
- Telebit Date:840210 (Container 222, Folder 25)
  96 Plus Modem Prototype; Internal Hardware Specification
- Telebit Date:840119 (Container 222, Folder 26)
  Discussion Draft; Questions & Answers on Telebit
- Telebit Date:840119 (Container 222, Folder 27)
  Internal Hardware Specification developed by Payne Freret
- Telebit Date:830001 (Container 222, Folder 28)
  Structure Management (Johnson, Hughs-Hartog, Wilson)
- Telebit Date:851205 (Container 222, Folder 29)
  Discussion Draft: Venture Summary, How Work, Finances, Background
- Telebit Date:841114 (Container 222, Folder 30)
  Board Meeting (Pres. Report, Finances, Strategy, Common Stock, etc.)
- Publications&Ref Date:750701 (Container 228, Folder 1)
  7 entries, July 1, 1975 to 1977
- Publications&Ref Date:780201 (Container 228, Folder 2)
  12 entries, Feb. 1978 to Oct. 6, 1990
- Publications&Ref Date:910621 (Container 228, Folder 3)
  14 entries, June 21, 1991 to Jan. 7, 1993
- Publications&Ref Date:950305 (Container 228, Folder 4)
  9 entries, March 5, 1995 to Oct. 1996
- Publications&Ref Date:970420 (Container 228, Folder 5)
  16 entries, April 20, 1997 to April 10, 1999
- Publications&Ref Date:000101 (Container 228, Folder 6)
  16 entries, Jan. 2000 to Jan. 24, 2001
- Publications&Ref Date:020001 (Container 228, Folder 7)
  17 entries, 2002 to June, 2004
- Publications&Ref Date:040506 (Container 228, Folder 8)
  5 entries, May 6, 2004 to Sept. 26, 2008
- Scrapbook Date:600823 (Container 233, Folder 1)
  L'Institut Babbage Va Retracer Une Histoire de L'Informatique, by Rex Malik (n/d)
- Scrapbook Date:600823 (Container 233, Folder 2)
  1960 IRE WESCON Convention Record
- Scrapbook Date:681023 (Container 233, Folder 3)
  FCC - Application for Federal Employment
- Scrapbook Date:690115 (Container 233, Folder 4)
  FCC - Travel Vouchers
- Scrapbook Date:690401 (Container 233, Folder 5)
  Law and Contemporary Problems, "Communications, Part 1"
- Scrapbook Date:710310 (Container 233, Folder 6)
  FCC - Final Decision and Order
- Scrapbook Date:710901 (Container 233, Folder 7)
  0the Future of the Telephone Industry, 1970 - 1985 (Baran & Lipinski)
- Scrapbook Date:730101 (Container 233, Folder 8)
  D-NET, IFF/ARPA (Including RECON: A Computer System for On-line Remote Group Conferencing
- Scrapbook Date:731001 (Container 233, Folder 9)
  The Futurist, "30 Services that Two-Way Television Can Provide" (by PB)
- Scrapbook Date:770001 (Container 233, Folder 10)
  Computers & Comm: Implications for Educ. "Inter 2-Way Comm via TV Cable to Home for Educ. Purposes - Why is Nothing Happening? By PB
- Scrapbook Date:770001 (Container 233, Folder 11)
  Some Perspectives on Networks - Past, Present and Future (by PB)
- Scrapbook Date:770616 (Container 233, Folder 12)
  World Future Society (Study of Alternative Futures)
- Scrapbook Date:770701 (Container 233, Folder 13)
  Technology and Privacy, Report of the Privacy Protection Study Commission (quotes PB)
- Scrapbook Date:770908 (Container 233, Folder 14)
  New Scientist, "Packet-switching's Unsung Hero" (PB who put digital coding into telecomm.)
- Scrapbook Date:771201 (Container 233, Folder 15)
  The Co Evolution Quarterly
- Scrapbook Date:781201 (Container 233, Folder 16)
  Planet News, "Computer Tele-conferencing: A Brief History"
- Scrapbook Date:780101 (Container 233, Folder 17)
  ICCC - 78 Keynote Speech, "Communication from an Info. Processing Viewpoint" (mentions PB)
- Scrapbook Date:781215 (Container 233, Folder 18)
  Business Week, "A Stampede to Packet Switching" (mentions PB)
- Scrapbook Date:790101 (Container 233, Folder 19)
  Visual Environmental Adaptation Problems of the Partially Sighted (prepared for HEW)
- Scrapbook Date:790917 (Container 233, Folder 20)
  Aviation Week & Space Technology, "Packet-Switching Seen for Weapons Use" (mentions PB)
- Scrapbook Date:800714 (Container 233, Folder 21)
  Mountain View Cable Television: A Proposal to the City of Mountain View, CA
- Scrapbook Date:800901 (Container 233, Folder 22)
  Cost Implications for Survivability of Terrestrial Networks under Malicious Failure
- Scrapbook Date:801218 (Container 233, Folder 23)
  Equatorial Comm. Co, A European Document (Patent Application) Designating PB as Inventor
- Scrapbook Date:811102 (Container 233, Folder 24)
  Computer-Based National Information Systems: Tech. & Public Policy Issues (US Office of Tech)
- Scrapbook Date:811111 (Container 233, Folder 25)
  Networks (an International Journal) - List of Members of Editorial Board (includes PB)
- Scrapbook Date:780915 (Container 233, Folder 26)
  Electronic Text Transmission Services - Impact upon Newsprint Consumption, 1988-1993, by PB
- Scrapbook Date:810803 (Container 233, Folder 27)
  Telecommunication Technology and Public Policy (PB on Special Panel on Tele. Technology)
- Scrapbook Date:811201 (Container 233, Folder 28)
  OAT List of Publications
- Scrapbook Date:820001 (Container 233, Folder 29)
  Packet Technologies - Brochure, Advisory Council and other info.
- Scrapbook Date:820101 (Container 233, Folder 30)
  OAT Assessment Activities
- Scrapbook Date:820304 (Container 233, Folder 31)
  What OTA Is, What OTA Does, How OTA Works (Office of Technology Assessment)
- Scrapbook Date:820315 (Container 233, Folder 32)
  Americans Win Ericsson Prize (Kleinrock & Roberts, Stockholm)